[speaker clicks on]
I know this is a big change,
but change can be good.
Right?
[boat creaks]
Yeah, this is going great. Cool.
Ready… Row!
Wait, what?
-[rower] Whoa, not ready, not ready!
-[rower 2] Starting?
["Whiplash" by Aespa playing]
[grunts]
Hey, we're lopsided.
-Okay, port! More power!
-Are you sure?
Uh… uh…
Sorry, starboard, more power.
Sorry, I'm used to facing the other way.
[Ryder] Port or starboard?
-Rate's too high!
-Uh…
-It's starboard!
-[Josh] Baloo, slow down.
He's rushing the slide!
-Okay, I know!
-Do you?
Baloo!
-Baloo, take it down!
-Trying!
-[Josh] Ratio!
-Okay! Wean off!
Ow!
Why're we stopping?
Hey, we kept the receipt, right?
We can still send her back?
Ha, ha, ha.
♪ Whip, whiplash ♪
♪ One more, give 'em whiplash ♪
[school bell ringing]
[Cabrera] To avoid Teagan's dismissal,
we can extend
a ten-day grace before payment.
-I trust that'll suffice.
-[laughs]
Ten whole days.
Is there a problem, Mrs. Tao?
Or is it Emerson?
I go by Emerson now.
Look, the education trust
has been implicated and seized,
and I really don't want to have
to pull Teagan out of another school.
If there's anything we could do…
Unfortunately, we've allocated
our financial aid for the year.
But we could set up an installment plan.
Would $7,000 each month work?
Well, that's… very generous.
Seems so doable.
Otherwise, there are
family-funded scholarships,
such as the Chou Scholarship,
awarded to students who the families feel
belong to the Easton community
and represent its values.
Ah.
Installment plan it is, then.
[knocking on door]
I assume you will be
at parents' night tonight.
Next Monday,
we'll get this tuition plan sorted.
[Ella] Okay.
Teagan's friend. What are you doing here?
She set fire to a car.
It's my car. I can do what I want with it.
-Did my parents call?
-No.
They'll take a jet to space,
but not Massachusetts.
[Josh] Okay, boys, keep heading up.
A little to the left.
Ready, and down.
[Quaid] Worst practice ever.
-[Baloo] Not the worst.
-[Josh] Speak for yourself.
You didn't lose a kidney because
the cox doesn't know her left from right.
Looks like that hurts.
Watch yourself, Faid.
Hey, I'm not sure why you're arguing
who sucked most.
It was a nine-way tie.
Not like we have a big race
or anything tomorrow.
-What race?
-Line it up, boys.
Come get your special event unis
for the alumni race.
It's Easton Spirit Week.
Every team has their event
leading into the Iron Crucible.
-The school-wide obstacle course.
-It's designed to kill you.
Wrong! It is designed
to build perseverance.
Legend says that in the last 100 years,
seven people have died.
Statistically, that's only
a 0.07% chance of death.
Our main event is the alumni race.
The old crew come back
and race the new team.
It's the passing of the torch.
Unless they beat us.
Then it's more of a handing us our asses.
So it's just a bunch of old dudes trying
to prove that they're still young and fit.
They're probably all
one steak away from a heart attack.
[laughing]
Actually, it's our dads.
And mine's an Olympian.
And mine's a world-record holder.
[laughs] We're going to get smoked.
-So glad my moms don't row.
-I don't want Dad to have a heart attack.
Okay, boys. Let's get the boat away.
Uh, hey, guys, has anyone seen my cox box?
-Your cox what?
-[Noah] What's missing?
-What?
-[Quaid] Saucy.
You know what it is.
The amplifier, the microphone thing--
Hands on the boat! Ready, up to shoulders.
And walk her in.
Hey, El. Doing the lunch rush
take you back?
Like I was 17 again. With shin splints.
I got your tips from the other night.
Don't spend it all in one place,
unless that place is here.
Hey, Jim, um…
Any chance you'd flip me an advance
for my next check?
It's for Teagan's school. I wouldn't ask
if you weren't my last resort.
I can front you a couple hundred.
Would that cover it?
God, no. [laughs]
But every little bit helps.
Thanks, Jim.
Hang in there, kid.
[exhales]
Ugh, where is it?
Harder than it looks, huh?
Yeah, getting eight boys to do anything
is impossible.
That's the job of a coxswain.
You gotta get them to follow you.
How?
You have to win minds and hearts.
Figure out what motivates them.
Look, you're, um… You're like a conductor.
You're not a musician.
You'll know soon enough
if coxing is for you or not.
Just like Baloo's learning
he's not for stroke seat.
Come on.
When the old boathouse burned down,
I thought it could use an upgrade.
This is all reclaimed wood.
There we are.
You know, I was the fourth Regis
to row in the stroke seat.
With my boy Josh in stroke,
he'll be the fifth.
Hm.
-Rich.
-Matt.
I was just showing
some of the other alums my boathouse.
Your boathouse?
Well, donated.
-Ah.
-This is Matt.
We were stern pair,
-the seven to my eight.
-Mm.
Even though he's coaching our competition,
he'll be in our boat tomorrow.
And how are we feeling
about our alumni team's chances?
-We've put our time in on the erg, right?
-[man] Sure have.
I hope your boys can give us
a run for our money.
Oh, they'll put up a fight. Don't worry.
-[Josh] Oh, way to choke in eight seat.
-[Baloo] Learned from the best.
[Baloo chuckles]
We'll lose the flop.
I wish Coach'd quit the character building
bullshit and put me back in.
I dunno, maybe Coach is looking
for other options in stroke.
[laughs] Like who?
You?
-[tense music playing]
-Why not me?
Yeah, sure.
I guess.
-Dad!
-[Richard Regis] There's the stroke seat.
How was practice?
You, uh, keeping the crew in rhythm?
-Yeah, getting there.
-Good.
You've got until tomorrow, anyway.
Think you're good enough to take me on?
Maybe we'll have to give you a head start.
Maybe. [laughs]
We'll see what you got.
With me being total shit out there,
I can't imagine you hate me
any less than the others?
I don't hate you.
But you were shit.
Yeah, that was rough.
-And the guys do not pull any punches.
-Yeah.
No one's going to go easy on you.
You swim or you sink.
I have to, or I can't keep training.
Can you give me any insight
into these guys?
Apparently to cox them,
you need to understand them.
[intriguing music playing]
Josh Regis.
The boy who would be king.
[Cam] His dad won four Haverford Cups
as stroke seat. Josh can't compete.
Next.
Josh's cousin Ryder.
He's less of an heir, more of a spare.
Baloo, real name Bronson.
He's the heart of the engine room
and crumbles under pressure.
He should be nowhere near eight seat.
Mom's a senator.
-Wait, is he Britney's brother?
-Twibling.
Their mom used two different surrogates
at the same time. Designer twins.
Wow, whoa. What is with this school?
Your four seat is our powerhouse.
Damon Quaid. New guy from the second boat.
Bit of a troublemaker,
as opposed to Noah Bainbridge.
-Cultured and refined, i.e. boring.
-[Noah] All of it.
But he takes rowing seriously
and expects everyone else to.
Perry Chou.
Always on trend, never on rhythm.
And Chris, a.k.a. Crabcatcher.
From the junior boat.
The nickname explains itself.
Thanks.
And you? Cam Dillinger. Lone wolf.
Only has eyes for the next clean catch.
[both laughing]
Yeah, pretty much.
All right. Enough chatter.
Let's hit the showers.
Teagan, your change room's down the hall.
Grab your things.
My cox box! Who did…? Di…
-Who's that?
-Ha, ha.
[Hayden] That is our new coxswain.
What happened to Liam?
-Well, how much experience does she have?
-Oh, lots.
She had her first practice today.
How's my son
supposed to lead the team with her?
Well, see, he doesn't have that problem.
Because he's not in stroke.
Okay, boys, listen up.
We need to win tomorrow, all right?
I'll talk to Coach and get back
in the eight. It's not up for discussion.
Yeah, if you wanna think inside the box.
Or… you could try me.
-Or me.
-Or the person with the best technique.
-And who's that?
-It's Cam.
[scoffs]
It's not Cam.
Cam's bladework is impeccable,
and he gets the most out of the boat.
He should get a shot.
[door slams]
[intriguing music playing]
[boys arguing indistinctly]
Ugh.
[muffled arguing, water running]
[Perry] Ryder's right.
We need fresh blood in stroke.
That's funny.
Hey, we don't have to argue.
Show of hands, who thinks
Perry should get a shot at stroke?
Wow, thanks, guys.
[Ryder] Dude,
you're not as good as your dad.
Anyone for Cam?
Didn't think so. And how about Ryder?
And that's two.
And who thinks it should be me?
-Whoa!
-[all clamoring]
-Ooh…
-Uh, sorry.
-What the hell?
What are you doing?
-I'm on the team. Don't I get a vote?
-Everyone knows who you're voting for.
All right, who's backing me?
-Then it's settled by popular vote.
-Yeah, except it's Coach's decision.
[Teagan] Exactly. Thank you.
-Can you get out of here?
-Yep. I am… Oh!
Sorry, Noah, I was not expecting that.
This cannot be the new normal.
[door closes]
[Teagan] Why are we going
to parents' night?
[Ella] We need to impress the families
so you can get a scholarship
and you don't get kicked out.
Recognize anyone?
I think saw my English teacher.
Waste of time. How hard can English be?
We have to find wealthy families
who'll think of you
when they're bequeathing.
[modern string quartet music playing]
Beautiful space, isn't it?
-My father donated it.
-[gasps]
Handpicked every piece of furniture.
Oh my gosh.
Gwendolyn Chou.
-I'm Ella. This is my daughter, Teagan.
-Hi.
Hi.
Ah.
The new coxswain.
I've heard about you from my son, Perry,
which means
you must be the wife of that… hotelier.
[Teagan, quietly] Abort, abort.
You know what?
-Wife can be a loose association.
-Would you excuse me?
[clears throat] Nice group of people.
Well, we tried.
[Hayden] How long do we have to be here?
[Lana] Just a couple of hours.
Goddamn parents' night.
You are so dramatic.
They're a bunch of hyenas.
-All these Karens.
-Hey!
What? It's a gender-neutral term.
They just think I'm for sale,
which I'm not.
You are overreacting. It's gonna be fine.
[woman] Coach Hayden.
I would love to chat with you about Ryder.
See?
-Bye.
-Hey!
His summer rowing coach
said he was going to make a call
-to the national team…
-Thank you.
…to put Ryder on his radar.
-I can see why. Ryder's doing well.
-I understand you're changing up stroke.
We're keeping our options open.
Of course. Oh, um…
Ryder mentioned
that some of the ergs need repair.
Would a new set help you out?
You know what? That's a generous offer,
but I'd have to run it by admin first.
Yeah.
-You enjoy your night. Yeah.
-Thank you.
[Hayden sighs] Goddamn parents' night.
So how is it that you're not in stroke?
Coach has been "experimenting."
It's only temporary.
It's an embarrassment, is what it is.
I'll get it back.
No. I will.
Where's Hayden?
Hi…
[laughing] Oh wow.
Okay, that was just ugly.
Ah…
-Here you go.
-[whispers] Thank you.
Teagan. Teagan's mom.
Ella.
Wanna sign up
for our parents' association?
-Mm-mm-mm.
-Oh.
-No, thank you.
-Um, where have you been?
I was gated. It's like house arrest,
but the school is my house.
Cabrera also has me working tonight.
Ella, you look hot.
Not like the drab moms.
Thank you. Not that it's helping
our cred in this room.
Yeah, it turns out fancy people
don't love it when your dad's a felon.
These Eagle's Cove elite
actually love a scandal.
Helps them feel better about themselves.
If that's true,
then… any attention is good attention.
-[Juliet] Hm?
-Anybody seen the bar?
Huh.
-What's up, dude?
-Hey, man.
-How's it going?
-Good.
You guys just get here?
-Yeah, we did.
-What's the deal with Josh and Ryder?
Oh, talk about scandals.
Josh's dad was the only heir
to the Regis empire,
and then it came out that his father
had an affair with the dog walker
and had a secret love child, Ryder's mom.
[Teagan] No way.
Josh and Ryder get along,
but, well, rumor is,
Josh's side of the Regis family
call Ryder's side the Egregiouses.
Yeah, so…
I haven't needed to drink this bad
since the FBI raided my house.
[gasps] The FBI raided your house?
It was horrible.
They tore through the house,
ruined the carpet,
and they took all my Birkins.
[gasps] I would've had
a breakdown right there.
I need more Chardonnay
just thinking about it.
-[gasps]
-[giggling]
[Ella] If you'll excuse me.
Not bad.
Hm?
The Easton moms.
You got them hanging on your every word.
Well played.
I don't think we've met.
We haven't. I'm Imogen.
So you're the woman whose husband
ripped everyone off and is now on the lam.
Ah.
Yeah.
Still less dysfunctional than mine.
[chuckles]
The sins of the husband
do not fall on the wife.
Welcome to the Easton circus.
-I should get back to my daughter.
-You should.
And by the way, this?
Don't change a thing.
Hi.
Did you just scandalize
your way into a scholarship?
I don't know,
but I think I've made a new friend.
Thank you.
-Have you seen Hayden?
-Mm.
Inside.
He's gone.
Thank you.
Better decide stroke seat
before they start hunting in packs.
Ugh. I've been offered everything
from a board seat at a tech start-up
to, I think, sexual favors.
Hm. Well, how lonely are you?
Mm.
[laughs] Seriously, though,
who's it gonna be?
I dunno.
I think I've got to take a chance.
Easton parents be damned.
Hey, Cam.
Coach, have you been hiding?
It's you. You're stroke.
Seriously?
You've earned it.
[laughs]
Thanks, Coach.
-[Richard] There you are.
-I've been meaning to catch up with you.
Look, I understand you're on
some sort of "everyone gets a turn" kick,
but enough's enough. You have
a tried-and-true stroke seat here.
I've made my decision.
You'll see it on the boat.
-Coach. Thanks.
-Well, I am very…
Dad, look. I think we know who he picked.
It's gonna be good.
We'll see about that.
[upbeat music playing]
You nervous?
Course not. It's only if I lose this,
I'll get kicked off the team,
and my rowing career will be over.
Wow, is it Bring Your Dad to Row Day?
Your dad's never missed a race.
-It's fine. I wouldn't want him here.
-Well, no.
But I bet you'd want that In-N-Out Burger
he always brought you.
-Mm.
-Hey, new pregame tradition.
-Let's go.
-What?
[soft music playing]
[Ella] It's a quiet spot, not far.
Growing up,
I used to come here with a friend.
An Easton rower, actually.
[loon calling]
Always thought this place
was kind of magical. Don't laugh.
[chuckles] I'm not. I like it.
I know your dad would have some kind of
pep talk for you for race day.
I'm sorry I don't have anything,
but be fast and don't fall in.
-That's good.
-[announcer] Attendees.
-The alumni race will begin in 30 minutes.
-Okay, I gotta go.
Okay.
All right. Break a leg or an oar.
Hey, there's been a change in plans,
but I will make it up to you.
Okay, listen up.
Josh, you're back in stroke.
-Oh…
-[Hayden] Cam in seven.
-Then Baloo, Quaid, and Ryder.
-[rower] Nice.
Clean catches, and remember
to use the full length of the stroke,
because if you do not,
we will whoop your ass.
[all exclaiming]
See you out on the water.
Let's go. Hustle.
It was out of my hands.
Not like a coach'd
make decisions for his boat.
Look, I get it, all right?
I rowed with Josh's dad. It's not fair.
I'm a better rower. I deserve it.
Yeah, but so did I.
Easton wants to see
a certain person in stroke.
They don't want a townie. They want
someone the Easton crowd can follow.
So, not us.
[Cam exhales]
I'm going to the Olympics one day, Coach.
Do you think Josh is?
[tense music playing]
Don't screw this up.
I got a lot riding on this.
I won't if you won't.
Two minutes to launch!
So what if your dads
won the Haverford Cup?
[Richard] All eight, watch descent.
Over head! Hands across! Roll it in!
Right foot in! Lean!
On jump! One, two, jump!
Lean!
Are we screwed?
[Perry] Big time.
[Teagan] Okay. [clears throat]
I was thinking we start with a sprint,
drop down, then back up
for the last 500 meters.
It's actually not a bad idea.
Let's try it.
[intense dance music playing]
-Ready… row!
-[horn blows]
-[Teagan] Steady. Give me five.
-[cox] Long and strong.
[Teagan] Four.
-Three.
-[cox] Okay, boys, find our rhythm.
[Teagan] All right, looking good here.
Pull up the rate. Let's give it a sprint.
[intense music continues]
Good work! We're pulling ahead!
Okay, let's take it down two beats.
Do it together.
Bring back!
Make it count. Come on!
[cox] Pick up the rate.
[Teagan] Win!
[cox] Close the gap. Sharp.
-Sharp!
-Hey, let's go earlier!
-Not yet. They'll get scrambly!
-I wanna go now!
Wait for my call! Don't push!
[Josh] I'm going! Pick it up, boys!
[Teagan] Josh!
You're off rhythm. Take it easy!
-[Quaid] Hey, wait up!
-See?
[Noah] We're getting smoked.
-Starboard needs power.
-[Crabcatcher] I can't keep up!
[Teagan] I told you they'd get scrambly.
Now we're way behind.
-Pull!
-[cox] The end's in sight.
Let's send it. One.
-Two.
-Go, go now!
Legs! You want to lose to your dads? Pull!
[horn blows]
[boys groaning]
-[Perry] Ugh, come on.
-[man] Eagle pride!
Yeah!
[men cheering]
Ugh!
-[men cheering and laughing]
-[cox] Told you!
Good guys!
You should've called.
You should've waited.
[indie music playing]
♪ Woke up every day
And I can feel it's always here ♪
[Richard laughing]
Looking good, crew.
Nothing like tradition, hm?
Losers serve the winners.
You'll get them next time.
Oh, so stingy with the potato salad.
That's better.
-[Britney] Mm, no fish for me.
-[Richard] Keep it coming.
Maybe next time
you'll actually listen to me.
[scoffs] Like you weren't
rushing the slide.
She's not wrong.
Catches were shit.
Excuse me?
Look, you're shit at coxing,
and you know it. You should just quit.
Lay off her. We had a bad race.
You don't have to cry about it.
[utensil clatters]
-Hey.
-[rower] Whoa.
Thanks, uh…
Though I can stand up for myself,
you know.
Oh, I'm well aware.
Maybe I should've listened to Josh.
At least we would've been in sync.
You're not the first coxie
to fight with your stroke seat.
Let it go.
It should've been you.
-Well, I guess Coach felt otherwise.
-Well, he's wrong.
Ugh, potato salad.
You shouldn't have eaten so much, doofus.
Iron Crucible in the morning.
It's not that bad, is it?
-Hey! Hi, Bronson.
-Hello.
So, um,
we need to talk about that pull pic.
It's cringe,
and you're going to embarrass Mom.
Why? Is there something on my face?
Uh…
It's a tad… thirsty.
[laughs]
Okay.
You found your man. Let me find mine.
She's got elections coming up.
If Mom has a problem with it,
she'll say something.
But she won't,
because look how cute I am in this. Oh.
[Britney laughs]
-[Baloo] Who is this?
-[Britney] Oh.
Okay. So he's hot. Whatever.
See, there's a method to my madness.
[Britney] If you're doing HIIT workouts…
Everyone! A few words.
[indistinct chatter]
To my fellow alumni.
-Eagle pride!
-[alumni] Eagle pride!
We've got a big season ahead of us.
This is the year we commit to each other.
-The year we…
-…take down Westvale, huh? Hm?
[alumni cheering]
Whoo, yeah!
[all clapping and cheering]
All right. Everybody have fun tonight,
but remember, don't stay up too late.
We've got the Crucible in the morning.
Carry on.
It's not exactly
the message I was going for.
Competition needs
a little bloodlust, Hayden.
You never liked that though.
It's part of the way you coach.
Josh is in the stroke. You had your say.
What'd it take, by the way?
Oh, uh, Principal Cabrera's niece
wanted an internship at Louis Vuitton.
Yeah. I made a call.
I want to win, man. Don't you?
-You can't buy a championship.
-Mm…
The sooner these guys understand that,
the sooner we'll get back to winning.
[tense music playing]
[exhales]
Nothing appealing?
Ah, I just finished
a three-hour lunch rush
serving clams, mussels, and scallops. So…
-You're mollusked out.
-Yeah.
Hot tip. I tried some of that apricot jam
from the dessert with the kielbasa.
Hm.
Mm… Mm!
Where did you learn that?
My husband owned
a chain of boutique hotels.
-We had weddings and galas.
-You're an event planner.
Not officially.
I'm just, like, the wife of the boss.
But clients liked my ideas, and I liked
planning their parties with them.
Your husband had money,
but you had the taste.
Turns out he didn't even have the money,
-so…
-[laughs]
Finding new party themes is hard.
I mean, everything is so overdone.
The trick is to find something
that's as unique as the client is.
Mm.
Like apricot kielbasa.
Are you busy two Saturdays from now?
James Bond-inspired casino night.
Do you wanna come?
Talk about things being overdone.
License to snooze, right?
It's actually my party.
-Oh.
-For my son's birthday.
He's a big Bond fan.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Ah. Forgive me. I get verbal blah.
When I'm tired, or any time, actually.
-Wanna tell me about the party?
-Oh, maybe another time.
[grunts]
Josh.
My first alumni race,
I lost to your grandfather.
It's a rite of passage.
That anger you feel, that fire,
that's the fuel you need to win.
[emotional music playing]
My second race,
I beat him by a boat length.
[laughs]
You'll get us next year.
I expect nothing less.
[ominous music playing]
[Ella] Matt Hayden?
[laughs]
I heard you were back in town.
And yet no gift basket.
That was wrong of me. I will do better?
[Ella laughs]
[Ella] Still come here, huh?
Someone had to hold down the fort
for the last 20 years.
You can't leave a view like this
unlooked at.
Well, thanks for your service.
My pleasure. [chuckles]
-How you been?
-Ah.
That's the question.
Wait, you really don't know.
You didn't even think to google me?
-I'm… sad?
-I'm not a screen guy.
Not like my daughter, Madison,
who you'll meet sometime.
She's a teen with a lot of opinions.
-Teenagers are the worst.
-Yeah, the worst.
-And it's just me.
-Mm.
-Single parenting is impossible.
-Mm-hmm.
I just live in constant fear
that Teagan will hate me forever.
Teagan's your daughter. Right.
Of course. I should have known.
That bullheadedness came from somewhere.
-Bullheaded? Me?
-[laughing]
I never once managed to change your mind.
I'm glad you're back.
-You seem good.
-I'm a shell of a woman.
Life is kicking my ass.
Come on.
You? The girl who got a second job
to buy a car to drive to her first?
No, that girl knows how to survive.
Remember that, huh?
I remember all of it.
Hey.
A few of us are going for a dip.
You wanna come?
[scoffs] No thanks, bruh.
You've been coming at me all day.
What's the matter, your dad?
He get you all riled up?
Don't talk to me about my family.
I'm a Regis too.
Or is that not convenient for you today?
I've always been there for you.
Your dad is such a dick to you.
And you just take it.
Yeah?
Well, your mom
is a grasping, status-hungry leech.
How egregious.
-[grunts]
-[rowers exclaiming]
[aggressive rock music playing]
Hey, stop!
[Baloo] Oh, shit.
[Cam] Guys. Guys, guys!
Guys, we're teammates!
[boy] Go, Ryder, go!
Guys, break it up!
[gasping]
-[Cam] Josh. Josh, don't, don't!
-No, no, no, no, no! [screams]
[exhales]
[laughing] Oh.
-You jackass!
-[yelling] Hey, you two! That's enough!
What a disgrace!
Clambake's over! Crew, go home!
And when I see you tomorrow,
I wanna see athletes, not children!
You got me?
Go!
[quiet, tense music playing]
[Cam] I don't think
I've ever seen Coach that mad.
[Teagan] He can join
the rest of the crew who's pissed at me.
[Cam exhales]
See you tomorrow.
Uh, I don't know, Cam. Look,
I don't think I'm right for this team.
A team that wants to fight me
isn't going to follow me.
That's too bad.
You're better than the last cox we had.
Pisses off Josh so much.
Yeah, it really does.
[Teagan laughs softly]
I hope I see you at the race.
You're tough enough. They should know it.
Are you sure about this?
It's 14 miles long.
Yeah, I got this.
[Cabrera] Welcome to the Iron Crucible!
Easton Prep was founded on a mission
of unlocking every student's potential.
Now, the purpose of the Iron Crucible
is not to finish, but to find your limits.
And every year, to exceed them.
Ready? Set…
Race!
["Run Rabbit" by Alt Blk Era playing]
The course is comprised
of seven obstacles,
each separated by a two-mile run.
♪ Run, rabbit, run, rabbit
Run, run, run ♪
Your wristbands let you check in
at each obstacle.
[beeping]
There's been a lot of bickering
about the stroke seat.
So I'm going to make this fun.
Whoever gets farthest wins stroke.
♪ …pulling me
Haven't had to run a mile since I was 17 ♪
[both grunting]
♪ Haven't had to tell myself
That you're a fever dream ♪
♪'Cause you said to me
Do you wanna fall? Hold my hand ♪
[beeps]
♪ Why d'you wanna talk? Just run fast ♪
♪ Don't you know it's all in your hands? ♪
♪ Now you wanna crawl out my past ♪
♪ Kicked out of the party ♪
♪ And they said, "Run, rabbit
Run, rabbit, run, run, run" ♪
[beeping]
♪ Run, run, run ♪
[groans]
♪ Run, run, run, rabbit ♪
Hey, do you know
where my kid is right now?
They never tell you anything.
You just have to wait
until your kid texts you that they're out.
No one ever finishes?
Some make it pretty far,
but the last obstacle,
they hit the literal wall.
Hey, look, I'm, uh, sorry
I was rude to you earlier.
You weren't.
You were being honest,
and I got huffy because you were right.
Casino night has been done to death.
It's a classic for a reason.
I'm sure it'll still be a good time.
I want it to be better than good.
I want it to be,
"thanks his mom on the Internet" good.
It will be if I plan it.
You? [laughs]
You know what?
I think that's a great idea.
So what's your usual budget?
100K and the fee is 15%?
[laughs]
Yes.
-Yes?
-We can make that work.
Okay.
[both laughing]
Ah!
[beeping]
[exhales]
["I wanna See You Try"
by Apoena Ferreira Frota playing]
[grunting]
[Baloo grunts]
[both grunting and groaning]
♪ You want the power back ♪
♪ I wanna see you try ♪
[Quaid moaning]
[Teagan] You okay?
♪ Try ♪
♪ I wanna see you try ♪
[Baloo] Come on, big boy.
I'll bring him back.
[Teagan] You don't wanna keep going?
I didn't even want to start.
♪ Please don't make me laugh
I wanna see you try ♪
♪ Anything that you can do
I bet I do it better than ♪
♪ You don't wanna play me
I could beat you with my left hand ♪
♪ I'll be winning in sweatpants
Making up my own touchstone dance ♪
♪ I don't think you understand
These kids are calling me Batman ♪
♪ You want this clout I have?
You want this money, right? ♪
♪ You wanna be this bad
You want this diamond, right? ♪
♪ Please don't make me laugh
Please don't make me laugh ♪
[Ryder] Shit, Cam's coming.
♪ You wanna be this bad
You want this diamond, right? ♪
[Josh] Yeah.
Better a two-man race for stroke
than three. Let's roll it up.
♪ Try ♪
♪ I wanna see you try ♪
Hey! Dickheads! That's not fair!
[song ends]
Hey.
-Wow. You made it.
-[Teagan laughs]
Teagan, you okay?
Yeah.
Hey, did you see any of the others?
-Yeah, Perry and Crabby…
-Good.
…tapped out at the Atlas carry,
and Noah bailed at the tire run. And…
-This is the cargo net climb?
-Yep.
But the net is…
Yeah.
The Regises decided
to screw everyone over and pull it up.
I've been trying to reach it.
Uh…
Well, I could reach it
if I got on your shoulders.
Hop on.
[EDM playing]
[Cam grunts]
-[Teagan] Ooh, you okay?
-Yeah, all good.
[Teagan] Okay.
[Teagan grunts]
♪ If you ask me who I wanna be ♪
♪ I'mma spell it out
So it's plain to see ♪
♪ K-A-S-S-I-E K-R-U-T-T-T-T ♪
♪ 'Cause I wanna be fast
And I wanna be free ♪
♪ Wanna be the best so I gotta be mean ♪
[grunting]
♪ Yeah, I wanna be fast
And I wanna be free ♪
We did it.
Let's get those Regises.
All right.
♪ K-I-S-S-I-N-G ♪
♪ Hold me in your arms
If you wanna feel free ♪
-[beeping]
-[grunts]
♪ K-I-S-S-I-N-G ♪
♪ Hold me in your arms
If you wanna believe ♪
♪ If you wanna be a freak like me ♪
[daunting music playing]
Ah…
I'm slowing you down.
-You gotta go.
-I'm not gonna bail on you.
I don't wanna be
the reason you lose stroke.
Go.
I'll see you at the line.
-Okay?
-Okay.
[exhales]
[groans] Okay. Keep going.
It's the farthest we've gotten.
Yeah.
But I won.
For now.
[both breathing heavily]
Man, I feel like
my legs are gonna fall off.
What?
How did you make it?
Nice try stranding me.
[beeps]
[chuckling]
[exhales]
Well, it looks like
you're settling for third.
[breathing heavily]
[whispers] Keep going.
[quiet, stirring music playing]
[groans]
[exhales]
[David] Teagan!
I can't do it Dad, it hurts too much.
I have to stop, okay?
[David] But that's just
the pain cave talking.
Your brain's telling your body to give up.
[laughs] And I agree.
[David] If you make it
through the pain cave,
you'll find
the only thing you need in life.
Yeah, what?
You'll find what you're made of.
Come on. You've got this.
[exhales]
["TRUST!" by Rebecca Black playing]
♪ I could spell it out for you ♪
No way.
♪ I'll be laid out for you ♪
♪ You can feel free to control ♪
♪ Keep it in motion, motion
Put me in position, keep it in motion ♪
That's insane.
[Josh] I mean,
her body weight makes it easier.
She's not going to make it.
What if she makes it?
♪ Can you handle?
Trust ♪
♪ Trust ♪
♪ I can handle you
Can you handle? ♪
♪ Trust ♪
-♪ Trust ♪
-[Teagan grunts]
♪ I can handle you
Can you handle? ♪
♪ Trust ♪
♪ Ooh, la-la
Get me goin' like ga-ga-ga ♪
[straining]
♪ Ooh, la-la
I can handle you, can you handle? ♪
♪ Trust, ooh, la-la
Get me goin' like ga-ga-ga ♪
♪ Trust
Ooh, la-la ♪
♪ I can handle you, can you handle? ♪
[straining]
♪ Shoot me to the stars, I'm so gone
Oh, your moan is my favorite song ♪
[grunting]
-[music slowly muffles]
-[gasping]
[heart beating rapidly]
[music continues, unmuffled]
♪ I can handle you, can you handle? ♪
Is someone actually finishing?
Is that your daughter?
[Ella] Oh my gosh, she did it.
-[Hayden] Holy hell.
-[Ella] Go, Teagan!
[ringing]
[crowd cheering and clapping]
[Ella] Go, Teagan!
[cheering continues]
[man] Well done, Josh!
[woman] Sweet, Josh!
[boy] Fuck, yeah!
You did it!
[boy 2] I told you, I told you!
You finished.
Hasn't been done in six years. Good job.
Too bad you let your cousin finish first.
Uh-huh.
[boy] Only four?
[Hayden] We are the only team
that had anybody finish.
Not just one, but four. I'm damn proud.
Ryder, Cam, Josh.
And you did it by following Teagan.
So try to remember that
at our next practice.
Ryder. You're in stroke.
All right, let's hit the showers.
I'm gonna take you out
for burgers and dogs. Let's go!
You proved yourself today.
You figured out what motivates them.
Daddy issues and spite? [laughs]
And grit.
[both laughing]
Yeah, I guess I got that from my dad.
You coming to dinner?
-Thanks, but I'm gonna hang with my mom.
-I'll see you at practice.
El, it was nice catching up with you.
So you two know each other?
Yeah.
He was the rower you used to know.
Yes, he was.
-Ah. Were you more than friends?
-No, we were not.
[Teagan] Mm-hmm.
Oh, you gotta tell me
how you finished that race. That's crazy.
Uh…
It was something that Dad taught me.
It's weird. Everything wrong
in our lives right now is… his fault.
But…
Yeah, he's the one that got me through.
[emotional music playing]
Delayed onset muscle soreness
is a cruel mistress.
What's all this?
This is a mood board for a birthday party.
I have my first client
as an event planner.
Have you ever planned an event before?
I've done tons of behind-the-scenes stuff.
I think I can handle one birthday party
for a teenage athlete.
Besides, this is gonna cover
your tuition for the term.
[doorbell rings]
That's my clients.
Please pretend you respect me.
Did you say athlete?
What sport?
-Mom, It's fine.
-I just put cover-up on that.
No.
Teagan.
Aren't you gonna let us in?
[intriguing music playing]
[music ends]